<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.arviceblot.eso-addon-manager</id>

    <name>ESO AddOn Manager</name>
    <summary>Manage addons for The Elder Scrolls Online</summary>
    <developer id="arviceblot">
        <name>
            arviceblot
        </name>
    </developer>

    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>MIT</project_license>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

    <description>
        <p>
            Update and install addons for ESO. Primarily built on Linux for Linux.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Install, remove, and search addons from esoui.com</li>
            <li>Cross-platform support for Linux, macOS, and Windows</li>
            <li>Specific support for ESO on the Steam Deck through Flathub</li>
            <li>Options to auto update Tamriel Trade Centre prices and HarvestMap data</li>
            <li>Light and dark UI themes</li>
            <li>Import managed addons from Minion</li>
            <li>Identify and install missing dependencies</li>
        </ul>
    </description>

    <url type="homepage">https://github.com/arviceblot/eso-addons</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/issues</url>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.arviceblot.eso-addon-manager.desktop</launchable>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/master/docs/images/main.png</image>
            <caption>Main view showing installed addons</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/master/docs/images/browse.png</image>
            <caption>Search and browse installable addons</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/master/docs/images/details.png</image>
            <caption>Browse addon details and images</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/master/docs/images/settings.png</image>
            <caption>Application settings and details</caption>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <releases>
        <release version="0.4.14" date="2025-12-09">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Version 0.4.14 brings a slinky-dinky fix for Steam Deck desktop mode.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Change: Update dependencies</li>
                    <li>Fix: App starting in fullscreen on Steam Deck desktop mode</li>
                    <li>Fix: Crash with empty addon file hash</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="0.4.13" date="2025-07-17">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Version 0.4.13 includes a new addon list view and settings options:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>New: Add option to check for addon updates on app launch</li>
                    <li>New: Add TamrielTradeCentre region selection (instead of always downloading NA and EU)</li>
                    <li>New: Add individual indicators for long-running tasks</li>
                    <li>New: URLs are now visible on hyperlink hover</li>
                    <li>New: Add application icon to native window titlebar (macOS, Wayland not supported yet)</li>
                    <li>Change: Addon list view is now more compact</li>
                    <li>Fix: Addon action buttons won't float away on resize</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="0.4.12" date="2025-06-09">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Version 0.4.12 includes minor security and bug fixes:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Change: Update dependencies</li>
                    <li>Change: Update flatpak runtime to 24.08</li>
                    <li>Fix: Compile-time warnings about deprecated functionality</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="0.4.11" date="2024-10-25">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Version 0.4.11 includes minor changes for Steam Deck and addon details:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Change: Remove bbcode parsing from UI. It will remain disabled until there is a proper solution for rendering bbcode formatted text</li>
                    <li>Change: Update dependencies</li>
                    <li>Change: Reduce app size</li>
                    <li>Fix: Pixels-per-point too large on Steam Deck</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="0.4.10" date="2024-06-02">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Version 0.4.10 includes backup/restore feature, minor fixes:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>New: Add backup/restore functionality, making addon lists more portable</li>
                    <li>New: Add indicator for main process tasks</li>
                    <li>New: Add EU support for TTC downloads (thanks Wedmer!)</li>
                    <li>Change: Update dependencies</li>
                    <li>Change: Set minimum window size</li>
                    <li>Change: Fullscreen mode on steamdeck to attempt resolution fix</li>
                    <li>Remove: No longer used dependencies</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="0.4.9" date="2024-02-20">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Version 0.4.9 brings images, bug fixes, and responsive layout improvements:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>New: Add screenshots view to details page.</li>
                    <li>New: Add category icons to addon lists.</li>
                    <li>New: Add file details view to details page.</li>
                    <li>New: Add light and dark mode toggles.</li>
                    <li>Change: Replace egui_file with rfd for native file dialogs.</li>
                    <li>Fix: Issue with minion import button not reporting progress correctly.</li>
                    <li>Fix: Addons lists not resizing.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="0.4.8" date="2024-02-15">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Version 0.4.8 is here with a major UI update and the following changes:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>New: Major internal changes to view handling and layout.</li>
                    <li>New: Game version support in addon detail view.</li>
                    <li>New: Author view. From any addon detail page, select the author name to see all other addons by them.</li>
                    <li>Change: AddOn lists now display all addons without truncating.</li>
                    <li>Change: Consolidated category and search pages for installing new addons.</li>
                    <li>Change: Missing dependencies are now reported on any missing addons.</li>
                    <li>Change: Missing dependencies view does not hog main window or prevent addon install.</li>
                    <li>Fix: Import from minion no longer results in endless spinner.</li>
                    <li>Fix: All relevant views now update on addon install status changes.</li>
                    <li>Fix: Onboarding now diplays on new installs.</li>
                    <li>Fix: Changing addon directory in settings should default to a valid directory in file dialog.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="0.4.7" date="2024-01-17">
            <description>
                <p>
                    This release brings the following changes and updates:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Update layout so tab bar is always visible.</li>
                    <li>Add raw text view option for addon descriptions and changelogs.</li>
                    <li>Change auto-update functionality to update all button.</li>
                    <li>Add install and update addon funcitonality to addon detail view.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
    <categories>
        <category>Utility</category>
    </categories>
    <keywords>
        <keyword>addons</keyword>
        <keyword>eso</keyword>
        <keyword>game</keyword>
        <keyword>mods</keyword>
    </keywords>
</component>
