<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.arviceblot.eso-addon-manager</id>

  <name>ESO AddOn Manager</name>
  <summary>A cross-platform, unofficial addon manager for The Elder Scrolls Online</summary>
  <developer_name>arviceblot</developer_name>
  <developer id="arviceblot">
    <name>
      arviceblot
    </name>
  </developer>

  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

  <description>
    <p>
      Update and install addons for ESO. Primarily built on Linux for Linux.
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Install, remove, and search addons from esoui.com</li>
      <li>Cross-platform support for Linux, macOS, and Windows</li>
      <li>Specific support for ESO on the Steam Deck through flatpak</li>
      <li>Options to auto update Tamriel Trade Centre prices and HarvestMap data</li>
      <li>Import managed addons from Minion</li>
      <li>Identify and install missing dependencies</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/arviceblot/eso-addons</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/issues</url>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.arviceblot.eso-addon-manager.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/master/docs/images/main.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/master/docs/images/browse.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arviceblot/eso-addons/master/docs/images/settings.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="0.4.8" date="2024-02-15">
      <description>
        <p>
          Version 0.4.8 is hear with a major UI update and the following changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>New: Major internal changes to view handling and layout.</li>
          <li>New: Game version support in addon detail view.</li>
          <li>New: Author view. From any addon detail page, select the author name to see all other addons by them.</li>
          <li>Change: AddOn lists now display all addons without truncating.</li>
          <li>Change: Consolidated category and search pages for installing new addons.</li>
          <li>Change: Missing dependencies are now reported on any missing addons.</li>
          <li>Change: Missing dependencies view does not hog main window or prevent addon install.</li>
          <li>Fix: Import from minion no longer results in endless spinner.</li>
          <li>Fix: All relevant views now update on addon install status changes.</li>
          <li>Fix: Onboarding now diplays on new installs.</li>
          <li>Fix: Changing addon directory in settings should default to a valid directory in file dialog.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.7" date="2024-01-17">
      <description>
        <p>
          This release brings the following changes and updates:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Update layout so tab bar is always visible.</li>
          <li>Add raw text view option for addon descriptions and changelogs.</li>
          <li>Change auto-update functionality to update all button.</li>
          <li>Add install and update addon funcitonality to addon detail view.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <categories>
    <category>Games</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>addons</keyword>
    <keyword>eso</keyword>
    <keyword>game</keyword>
    <keyword>mods</keyword>
  </keywords>
</component>